They left for war as boys, never to return as men.
All Quiet on the Western Front is a war, drama, tv
movie film directed by Delbert Mann.
At the start of World War I, Paul Baumer is a
young German patriot, eager to fight.
Indoctrinated with propaganda at school, he and his friends
eagerly sign up for the army soon after graduation.
But when the horrors of war soon become too much to bear, and as his friends die or become gravely wounded,
Paul questions the sanity of fighting over a few hundreds yards of war-torn countryside.
Paul Bäumer, played by Richard Thomas.
Stanislaus Katczinsky, played by Ernest Borgnine.
Kantorek, played by Donald Pleasence.
Himmelstoss, played by Ian Holm.
Paul's Mother, played by Patricia Neal.
Josef Behm, played by Paul Mark Elliott.
All Quiet on the Western Front is an epic anti-war
television film produced by ITC Entertainment.
It was released on November 14, 1979.
Based on the 1929 book of the same name by Erich Maria
Remarque, it stars Richard Thomas and Ernest Borgnine.
Directed by Delbert Mann, this film is a joint British and American production
for which most of the filming took place in Czechoslovakia.
The film explores themes of france, germany, world war i, westfront, soldier.
The tone is emotional.